americasarmy.com 2014-04-01

# America's Army: Privacy Policy

_AmericasArmy.com_ is committed to protecting your privacy. Therefore, your use and implementation of the information and information request forms included in this web site are covered under the following guidelines. If you have any questions or comments about the information presented here, please contact the Webmaster. 

**AUTHORITY:** Collection of this information is authorized by Title 10 of U.S. Code, section 3013. 

**PRINCIPAL PURPOSE:** Information collected will only be used for security and identification. 

**ROUTINE USES:** Statistical and demographic analysis. 

**DISCLOSURE:** Voluntary, however, failure to provide the information may prevent participant from entering web site. 

###  PRIVACY 

####  1\. Information Collected and Stored Automatically 

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit: " The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain), and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website, " The type of browser and operating system used to access our site, " The date and time you access our site, " The pages you visit, and " If you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website, " If you link from our website to another website, the address of that website We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors -- to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits. 

####  2\. Cookies 

For site navigation purposes only, cookies are used in a limited manner. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. 

This website does not use persistent cookies (persistent tokens that pass information back and forth from the client machine to the server). We may use session cookies (tokens that remain active only until you close your browser) in order to make the site easier to use. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a web site if you do so. 

####  3\. If You Send Us Personal Information 

If you choose to provide us with personal information, such as by sending an e-mail or by filling out a form and submitting it through our Web site, we will use that information to respond to your message or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. Remember that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. If your communication is sensitive or includes personal information you may prefer to send it by postal mail instead. 

We may share the information you give us with another government agency if your inquiry relates to that agency. In other limited circumstances, such as responses to requests from Congress and private individuals, we may be required by law to disclose information you submit. Before you submit personal information, such as on an online form, you may be given more specific guidance as to how your personal information may be used. 

Electronically submitted information is maintained and destroyed according to the principles of the Federal Records Act and the regulations and records schedules of the National Archives and Records Administration and in some cases may be covered by the Privacy Act and subject to the Freedom of Information Act. 

###  SECURITY 

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this Government computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Anyone using this system expressly consents to such monitoring and is advised that if such monitoring reveals evidence of possible abuse or criminal activity, such evidence may be provided to appropriate law enforcement officials. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act. 

###  ACCESSIBILITY 

The United States Army is dedicated to making all information and technology available to individuals with disabilities. In 1998, Section 508 of the Rehabilitation Act Amendments, as amended by the Workforce Investment Act of 1998, issued accessibility standards setting forth electronic and information technology performance criteria. As amended, Section 508 requires that when Federal agencies develop, procure, maintain, or use electronic and information technology, they must ensure that this information is accessible to every individual. 

Using accessibility guidelines, we are continuously improving our web pages for easy access to all visitors. The U.S. Army is making every effort to bring our web site into Section 508 compliance, and will continue with these efforts as new methods and technology becomes available. 

If you find a problem that prevents access or you have any comments or questions about our policies, please contact our legal department.
